[
    {
      "title": "Round 6: Anything Related to the Colour Purple"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which legendary rock band shares its name with a shade of purple?",
      "answer": "Deep Purple"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which writer published the novel ‘The Color Purple’ in 1982?",
      "answer": "Alice Walker"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which artist's 1984 album features the title track ‘Purple Rain’?",
      "answer": "Prince"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which U.S. military decoration is awarded to service members wounded or killed in action?",
      "answer": "The Purple Heart"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Historically, due to its rarity and cost, purple dye became associated with which social class?",
      "answer": "Royalty (nobility)"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which purple dinosaur featured on a children’s TV show is known for the song ‘I Love You’?",
      "answer": "Barney"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which purple flower is a staple in aromatherapy due to its soothing fragrance?",
      "answer": "Lavender"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which fruit’s name is used as a common term for a deep shade of purple, especially in Europe?",
      "answer": "Aubergine (Eggplant)"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which Disney villain, characterized by a purple color palette and magical staff, appears in ‘Sleeping Beauty’?",
      "answer": "Maleficent"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which Ghost-type Pokémon from Generation I is predominantly purple and evolves from Haunter?",
      "answer": "Gengar"
    }
  ]